[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the first NFL team to win the Super Bowl indoors.", "correct_answer": "Dallas", "incorrect_answers": ["Tampa Bay", "Miami", "Pittsburgh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river flows through ten European countries and is the longest in the European Union?", "correct_answer": "Danube", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhine", "Dnieper", "Elbe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the movie Scream hit the theaters?", "correct_answer": "1996", "incorrect_answers": ["1997", "1995", "1994"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these vitamins is fat-soluble and is found in the milk fat?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin K", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B5", "Vitamin P", "Vitamin C"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Charlton Heston, who starred in Ben Hur and the Ten Commandments, also appeared in a war film about a Norman knight who falls for a village girl. What was the film?", "correct_answer": "The Warlord", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dark Tower", "De Le Creux", "The Vikings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clancy Brown, who played Captain Byron Hadley in The Shawshank Redemption, appeared in a 1983 movie with actor Sean Penn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A turtles lungs quickly break down, becoming less and less efficient over its lifetime.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A \u201ccombination lock\u201c has three integers. Each integer is a member of this set: {0, 1, 2, 3, 4,}. How many such locks with different combinations can be made?", "correct_answer": "125", "incorrect_answers": ["21", "15", "120"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the character of Joseph T. Wladislaw in The Dirty Dozen?", "correct_answer": "Charles Bronson", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Brown", "George Kennedy", "Lee Marvin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The eyes of a baby weigh about 1/400 of its entire body mass. How much do the eyes of an adult weigh?", "correct_answer": "1/4000 of the body mass", "incorrect_answers": ["1/1000 of the body mass", "1/20000 of the body mass", "1/10000 of the body mass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the fundamental beliefs of ayurveda is that five elements form the Universe and everything in it including the human body. These elements are earth, fire, water, air and which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Space", "incorrect_answers": ["Rock", "Wood", "Phlegm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Riga is the capital of which Baltic country?", "correct_answer": "Latvia", "incorrect_answers": ["Estonia", "Lithuania", "Belarus"]}]